Prehistoric life...
It is a general term for organisms that once inhabited the Earth.
After death, over a long period of time,
they turned into fossils within the strata.
Paleontology. It is the study of fossils,
exploring mechanisms such as biological evolution and interactions with the environment...
Keep it down! Hey...
Seriously, you're way too loud!
Huh? There's no one here.
Eh? What?
I am the club president, Tetori Kitadani!
Welcome to the Paleontology Club!
You're a prospective member, right?
No, I'm not!
I'm Kanna Nakazato from the Idol Research Club next door!
Behold! This is an ammonite fossil that I excavated!
Hey, listen to me!
Ammonites were amazing prehistoric creatures that thrived in oceans all over the world!
Also, the strata where these fossils are found are mainly Mesozoic, proving that other organisms excavated in the same layer lived in the same era!
In short, for paleontology, ammonites are key index fossils that tell us the era!
Huh...
An index fossil that reveals the era...
You accepted the fossil! Now, welcome to the world of SERIOUS PALEONTOLOGY!
W-W-What is happening?!
EXPLOSION! Prehistoric Silhouette Quiz!
Huh?! What is this place?
If you can't get every question right, you have to join the club!
EH?
Here comes Question 1!
Which dinosaur is this silhouette?
Huh? How should I know?!
Time is running out! Can you solve this question?
Huh? Uh, jeez... A Tyrannosaurus... or something?
How did you know?!
I just named the only dinosaur I know!
This is...
A Tyrannosaurus reconstruction unveiled in 2014!
Behold its feather-covered body!
It looks so fluffy!
Wait, wasn't Tyrannosaurus,
supposed to look different?
That is an outdated theory!
This one is becoming the mainstream view today!
Is that so?
Theories about dinosaurs advance every day!
That is the true thrill of paleontology!
FINAL QUESTION!
Which dinosaur is this silhouette?
Another super hard one?!
There are over 1,000 species of dinosaurs!
Can you get it right?
That's way too many!
Answer me! Or join the club!
Oh no,
I really have no clue!
Now answer!
3, 2, 1 until you join...
Tyrannosaurus!
How did you know?!
Hey, I should be asking that! Why is it the same answer?!
Allow me to explain!
In 1920,
it happened the world's first Tyrannosaurus reconstruction, made by Henry Osborn, the man who named it!
BUT!
As researchers studied other fossils and skeletal structures, the idea that they stood parallel to the ground,
became the consensus!
A prehistoric creature and a true idol of the dinosaur world...
THIS WAS...
Tyrannosaurus!
Tyrannosaurus...
An idol of the dinosaur world...
It's my loss...
I don't know how, but I won...
It’s a myriad of things that change over time and with the urgencies of everyday life...
Hey,
I hear someone muttering inside the locker!
Huh?
H-How can you hear that?
Hey, w-wait!
Hello there, sorry for intruding.
WHAT IS THAT???